optiontrade.com 2015-03-16

# PRIVACY POLICY

                 HF Markets Europe Ltd.
                      PRIVACY POLICY
                                          1
                            HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
      Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
             Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy statement covers the website www.optiontrade.com and any other related
websites that are registered and operated by the Company.
1. Application ....................................................................................................................................3
2. Personally Identifiable Information.................................................................................................3
3. Agents ...........................................................................................................................................3
4. Privacy ...........................................................................................................................................3
5. Legal Disclaimer .............................................................................................................................3
6. Choice/Opt-out ..............................................................................................................................4
7. Cookies ..........................................................................................................................................4
8. Security and Protection of your Personal Information .....................................................................4
9. Access to Personally Identifiable Information..................................................................................5
10. Legal Disclaimer ...........................................................................................................................5
11. Changes in this Privacy Statement ................................................................................................5
12. Collection of Information ..............................................................................................................5
13. Confidentiality Obligations ...........................................................................................................6
14. Right of Access .............................................................................................................................7
15. Transmittal ..................................................................................................................................7
16. Records ........................................................................................................................................7
17. Recordings ...................................................................................................................................8
18. Contact ........................................................................................................................................8
                                                                         2
                                                        HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                           Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                                     Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
                  Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

1. Application
In order to open an account with HF Markets (Europe) Ltd., you must first complete and send
the application form attaching the required documents. By completing the application form you
are requested to give private information in order to enable the Company to evaluate your
application and comply with Laws and Regulations governing the provision of financial services.
This information is also used to contact you about the Company's services.
2. Personally Identifiable Information
We do share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties solely for statistical purposes
and in an effort to better improve the Company’s marketing campaign and to the extent
allowed by the Terms and Conditions already accepted by you.
3. Agents
We use a card processing company for your deposits and withdrawals to and from your account.
This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any
other purposes.
4. Privacy
Any personal information you provide us will be treated as confidential and shared only within
the Company, its affiliates and its business partners and will not be disclosed to any third party
except under any regulatory or legal proceedings as well as to third parties that solely provide
statistical services to the Company to improve its marketing campaign. Web site tracking
systems may also collect data detailing the pages you have accessed, how you discovered this
site, the frequency of visits and so on. The information we obtain is used to improve the
content of our web site and may be used by us to contact you, by any appropriate means, and
to provide you with any information we believe may be useful to you.
5. Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and
when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a
judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
                                                         3
                                           HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                     Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                            Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
               Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

6. Choice/Opt-out
If you no longer wish to receive any promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving
them by following the instructions included in each communication.
You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not
our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share
your information with that party.
7. Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We
use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally
identifiable information you submit while on our site.
We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie does not expire
when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended
period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your
Internet browser's “help" file.
We set a persistent cookie for statistical purposes. Persistent cookies also enable us to track
and target the location and the interests of our users and to enhance the experience of our
services on our site.
If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but you will not be able to use myOptionTrade
and submit your application form.
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over
these cookies.
8. Security and Protection of your Personal Information
The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of
the Site or of the Services is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is
protected in many ways. You can access your Registration Information through a password
selected by you. This password is encrypted and known only to you. Your password must not be
                                                         4
                                           HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                     Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                            Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
               Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

revealed to anyone. Registration Information is safely stored on secure servers that only
authorized personnel have access to via password. The Company encrypts all personal
information as it is transferred to the Company and thus makes all necessary effort to prevent
unauthorized parties from viewing any such information.
Personal information provided to our Company that is not Registration Information also resides
on secure servers and is again accessible only to authorized personnel via password. This
information cannot be online accessible by you, therefore no password shall be selected to
view or modify this information.
9. Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, you must inform us by emailing our
Customer Support at support@optiontrade.com
10. Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and
when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a
judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We will not be liable
for misuse or loss of personal information resulting from cookies on our website that we don’t
have access to or control over. We will not be liable for unlawful or unauthorized use of your
personal information due to misuse or misplacement of your passwords, negligent or malicious,
however contacted.
11. Changes in this Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement,
the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we
collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it
frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by
means of a notice on our home page.
12. Collection of Information
                                                         5
                                           HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                     Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                            Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
               Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

The Company may collect client information directly from the Client (in his completed Account
Opening Application Form or otherwise) or from other persons including, for example, credit
reference agencies, fraud prevention agencies, other financial institutions and the providers of
public registers.
13. Confidentiality Obligations
Client information which the Company holds is to be treated by the Company as confidential
and will not be used for any purpose other than in connection with the provision,
administration and improvement of the Services, for research and statistical purposes and for
marketing purposes (if the Client’s consent is obtained where he is a natural person) and as
provided for under the paragraph below. Information already in the public domain, or already
possessed by the Company without a duty of confidentiality will not be regarded as confidential.
The Client agrees that the Company has the right to disclose Client information (including
recordings and documents of a confidential nature, card details, personal details) in the
following circumstances:
    a. where required by law or a competent Court;
    b. where requested by CySEC or any other regulatory authority having control or jurisdiction
    over the Company or the Client or their associates or in whose territory the Company has
    Clients;
    c. to relevant authorities to investigate or prevent fraud, money laundering or other illegal
    activity;
    d. to execution venues or any third party as necessary to carry out Client Instructions or
    Orders and for purposes ancillary to the provision of the Services;
    e. to credit reference and fraud prevention agencies, third authentication service providers
    and other financial institutions for credit checking, fraud prevention, anti-money laundering
    purposes, identification or due diligence checks of the Client. To do so they may check the
    details the Client supplied against any particulars on any database (public or otherwise) to
    which they have access. They may also use Client details in the future to assist other
    companies for verification purposes. A record of the search will be retained by the Company;
    f.to the Company’s professional advisors provided that in each case the relevant professional
    shall be informed about the confidential nature of such information and commit to the
    confidentiality herein obligations as well;
    g. to other service providers who create, maintain or process databases (whether electronic
    or not), offer record keeping services, email transmission services, messaging services or
                                                          6
                                            HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                      Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                             Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
                Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

    similar services which aim to assist the Company collect, storage, process and use Client
    information or get in touch with the Client or improve the provision of the Services under
    this Agreement;
    h. to data reporting service providers;
    i. to other service providers for statistical purposes in order to improve the Company’s
    marketing, in such a case the data will be provided in an aggregate form;
    j. to market research call centers that provide telephone or email surveys with the purpose
    to improve the services of the Company;
    k. where necessary in order for the Company to defend or exercise its legal rights;
    l. at the Client’s request or with the Client’s consent;
    m. to an Affiliate of the Company.
14. Right of Access
In the event that the Client is a natural person, the Company will use, store, process and handle
personal information of the Client, in accordance the Processing of Personal Data (Protection of
the Individual) Law of 2001.
If the Client is an individual, the Company is obliged to supply the Client, on request, with a
copy of personal data which it holds about the Client (if any), provided that the Client pays an
administrative fee.
15. Transmittal
By entering into an Agreement with the Company, the Client will be consenting to the
transmittal of the Client’s personal data outside the European Economic Area, according to the
provisions of Processing of Personal Data (Protection of the Individual) Law of 2001.
16. Records
Under Applicable Regulations, the Company will keep records containing Client personal data,
trading information, account opening documents, communications and anything else which
relates to the Client for at least five years after termination of the Client Agreement.
                                                           7
                                             HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                       Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                              Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
                 Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment

17. Recordings
Telephone conversations between the Client and the Company may be recorded and recordings
will be the sole property of the Company. The Client accepts such recordings as conclusive
evidence of the Orders/Instructions/Requests or conversations so recorded.
18. Contact
The Client accepts that the Company may, for the purpose of administering the terms of the
Agreement, from time to time, make direct contact with the Client by telephone, fax, or
otherwise.
                                                        8
                                          HF MARKETS EUROPE LTD
                    Regulated by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC)
                           Licence Number 183/12 - Registration Number 277582
              Risk Warning: Binary Option Trading is risky and you may lose all of your investment
